bestwaytoinvest.com 2016-05-28

# Privacy Policy - ForexNews.com

## Security and Disclaimer

###  _High Risk Investment_

ForexNews respects each individual’s right to privacy. We value our relationship with you, and we take pride in maintaining loyalty and respect with each individual user by providing you with security. The provisions of this notice apply to former users as well as our current users.

###  _Personal Information_

When you apply for or maintain a registration with ForexNews, we collect personal information about you for business purposes, processing your requests, informing you about products and services that may be of interest to you, and providing customer service. Such information may include information you provide when registering such as name, email, address, date of birth, etc.

###  _About Cookies_

Cookies are small files containing information that a Web site uses to track its visitors. ForexNews may set and access ForexNews cookies on your computer, enabling us to learn which advertisements and promotions bring users to our Web site. ForexNews may use cookies in connection with ForexNews’s products and services to track your activities on our Web sites. Such information that we collect and share would be anonymous and not personally identifiable.

###  _Sharing Information With Our Affiliates_

We may share personal information described above with our affiliates for business purposes, such as, but not limited to, servicing customer accounts and informing customers about new products and services, and as permitted by applicable law. Our affiliates may include companies controlled or owned by us as well as companies that have an ownership interest in our company. The information we share with affiliates may include any of the information described above. Our affiliates maintain the privacy of your information to the same extent ForexNews does in accordance with this Policy.

###  _Sharing Information with Third Parties_

ForexNews does not disclose your personal information to third parties, except as described in this Policy. Third party disclosures may include sharing such information with non-affiliated companies that perform support services for your account or facilitate your transactions with ForexNews, including those that provide professional, legal, or accounting advice to ForexNews. Non-affiliated companies that assist ForexNews in providing services to you are required to maintain the confidentiality of such information to the extent they receive it and to use your personal information only in the course of providing such services and only for the purposes that ForexNews dictates.

We may also disclose your personal information to third parties to fulfill your instructions or pursuant to your expressed consent.

We want you to know that ForexNews will not sell your personal information.

###  _Regulatory Disclosure_

Under limited circumstances, ForexNews may disclose your personal information to third parties as permitted by, or to comply with, applicable laws and regulations. For example, we may disclose personal information to cooperate with regulatory authorities and law enforcement agencies to comply with subpoenas or other official requests, and as necessary to protect our rights or property. Except as described in this privacy policy, we will not use your personal information for any other purpose, unless we describe how such information will be used at the time you disclose it to us or we obtain your permission.

###  _Opt Out_

You are not required to supply any of the personal information that we may request; however, failure to do so may result in our being unable to provide services to you. While we make every effort to ensure that all information we hold about you is accurate, complete, and up to date, you can help us considerably in this regard by promptly notifying us if there are any changes to your personal information.

If you do not wish to have your personal information disclosed to our affiliates or other third parties as described in this Policy, please contact us via e-mail at: [info@forexnews.com](mailto:info@forexnews.com)

or send your request to:

ForexNews  
Attention: CEO  
55 Water Street, 50th Floor  
New York, NY 10041  
(888) 503-6739
